Konstantin Khitrykh

Senior Developer

Profile

Unity/C# developer with 6+ years of experience, enthusiastic in game development.

Now I work on mobile F2P project in Matryoshka Games company in Novosibirsk. I learn several another languages (like Java, Erlang, JavaScript, Go, Kotlin and more), write some articles and develop open-source projects for study purposes. Earlier I had some experience in Python, C++, and PHP.

Employment History

Senior Developer at Matryoshka Games, Novosibirsk

April 2018 - Present

- New features implementation
- Create tools for performance analysis
- Server-side development
- Technical leadership
- Optimization
- Refactoring
- Code review

Middle Developer at Deus Craft, Novosibirsk

April 2016 - April 2018

- New features implementation
- Setup content extensions
- Operations with 2D content
- Native plugins integration
- Optimization

Technical Team Lead at Academ Media, Novosibirsk

July 2013 - April 2016

- Games and applications development
- Tools and templates development/support
- External services integration
- Project and team management
- Dev training process

Education

Bachelor's degree, Novosibirsk Institute of Economics and Management, Novosibirsk

September 2009 - July 2013

Information Technology course

Courses

Details

Novosibirsk, Russia, +79529456615 konh@yandex.ru

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ko nhit https://konh.github.io/

Skills
C#
Unity
C++
Java
Go
Python

Languages

Russian

English

C++ White Belt, Coursera

October 2017 - December 2017